visitusa.com 2016-11-02

# VisitUSA - Privacy

---  
| **Privacy Assured** | [](http://visitusa.com/visitusa/privacy#top)  
---|---  
TravelAffiliatePro.com absolutely guarantees your privacy when you use our services. Although we must gather some personal information in order to complete your hotel room reservation, we will zealously protect this information and will never reveal it except as specified in this policy. We will never abuse your trust or misuse your personal information.  
| **The Information We Collect** | [](http://visitusa.com/visitusa/privacy#top)  
---|---  
When you book a hotel room through TravelAffiliatePro.com, we require personally identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, and credit card information. We use this information only as necessary to book your hotel room(s). We will never sell, barter, give away, or otherwise reveal any of your personal information except as necessary to accomplish the reservation. When you use the "Tell a Friend" feature to send information about a certain hotel to someone else, we require the friend's name and email address. We will only use this information to tell them about your selected hotel.   
| **How We Use Your Information** | [](http://visitusa.com/visitusa/privacy#top)  
---|---  
Hotels require your credit card information in order to allow you to reserve a room. Therefore, we gather your credit card information as a guarantee for the hotel in which you are booking a room, and we send that information to that hotel. The hotel may charge your credit card a cancellation fee if you fail to check in on the date of your reservation or if you cancel your reservation after the hotel's cancellation deadline. 

Our partner Worldspan, a service that provides information about online travel prices, connects us to the hotel chains; hence, through the booking process, we give your information to Worldspan, which sends it to the hotel chains, solely for the purpose of guaranteeing your reservation. TravelAffiliatePro.com does not store your credit-card information or charge your credit card. 

We will use your email address to send you a confirmation of your reservation. We may also send you periodic emails about our site and about special deals on hotel rooms. You can opt out of these emails at any time.  
  
| **Credit Card Safety** | [](http://visitusa.com/visitusa/privacy#top)  
---|---  
We are very serious about protecting your credit card information. To ensure your safety and privacy, we use a secure server that encrypts your credit card number and encodes it into a non-usable form. When you are asked to enter your information, you can identify whether the page is secure by noting the change in the URL; instead of beginning with "http://", the page's URL should begin with "https://". The "s" notes that the page is secure, that our 128-bit encryption is in effect, and that your information is safe. 

Travelaffiliatepro.com does not charge your credit card and does not store your credit card information. We only send the information to the hotel in which you are booking a room, through Worldspan, in order to guarantee your reservation. 

Travelaffiliatepro.com guarantees secure, fraud-free reservations of hotel rooms. You can use our services confidently, knowing that your personal information is carefully protected. 

Although we absolutely guarantee your privacy and safety, we recommend that you follow commonsense online safety rules when making reservations through the Internet, at Travelaffiliatepro.com or anywhere else. We recommend that you install up-to-date anti-fraud and anti-virus software in order to prevent computer hackers from transferring your information to illicit users.  
  
---|---  
Throughout your visits to TravelAffiliatePro.com, we store general, anonymous data about your activity and your personal information. This information is not connected to you specifically; we gather this data in order to analyze users' needs, profiles, and patterns of behavior so that we can understand our clients better, improve our website, and enhance your experience with Travel Affiliate Pro.  
---|---  
TravelAffiliatePro.com uses cookies, which are small pieces of text that store general information about your visits. Cookies are a standard Web function and are not malware, adware, spyware, or any type of virus. We use cookies to analyze aggregate user data and to control what advertisements you see on our site. Cookies never store your sensitive personal data such as credit card information. 

You can disable cookies on your Web browser by changing your browsing options or settings.  
  
| **Advertisements** | [](http://visitusa.com/visitusa/privacy#top)  
---|---  
When you visit TravelAffiliatePro.com, you may view advertisements that are posted on the site by Google or by other companies. These advertising companies may collect information about you while you are visiting this website and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements, both here on this website and elsewhere on the Internet, about products and services that you might like. TravelAffiliatePro.com does not collect such information or control the content of the advertisements. You may be able to opt out of such advertising. To learn more about Google and its DoubleClick DART cookies that are used to generate interest-based advertising, click on this link. 

If you use TravelAffiliatePro.com without opting out of those advertisements, then you confirm that you understand and agree to this data collection so that we can display advertisements that may interest you.   
  
| **Changes to This Policy** | [](http://visitusa.com/visitusa/privacy#top)  
---|---  
Occasionally, TravelAffiliatePro.com will alter this privacy policy. All changes will be reflected in this document, on this webpage. Therefore, please check this page periodically so that you are always aware of the current version of this policy.   
| **Legal Disclaimer** | [](http://visitusa.com/visitusa/privacy#top)  
---|---  
Although we guarantee your privacy and the security of your information, we will disclose this information to the proper authorities if we are obligated by law to do so.   
| **Questions about This Policy** | [](http://visitusa.com/visitusa/privacy#top)  
---|---  
If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy or about this policy, please feel free to contact us through our query forms or by calling 614-408-8271.
